(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-30T02:49:54.711871",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Crazyになるほど恋しているZOMBIE
[A Zombie So in Love, It's Going Crazy]
HOLOLIVE INDONESIA SECOND GENERATION
KUREIJI OLLIE PRESENT
[Kureiji Ollie Presents]
Muka kagetmu lucu banget, sih!
Your startled face is so cute~
Kaget 'kan? Gitu~
You were startled, right? Haha~
Ini 'kan yang kamu nanti-nantikan?
Wasn't this what you were waiting for~
Bisa bicara sama oshi~
To be able to talk to your oshi~
Ngapain tuh memencet tombol back?
Hmm, why the frantic button pressing, dear?
Jangan-jangan... kamu nggak suka Ollie ngomong langsung gini?
Don't tell me you actually dislike this kind of interaction~
Aaaah! HP-nya kok dimatiin, sih?!
Aww, why'd you turn off the phone?
Beneran nggak suka ngomong sama Ollie, ya?
You really don't want to talk to me, huh~
Keseruan baru akan dimulai sekarang!
The fun is just about to begin~
Darling~
存在証明 愛だって 愛だって 吐いたって
Proof of existence, even if I spit out that "it's love, it's love,"
嗚呼 寝転んゴロンて 嫌ん嫌ん プリティプリティ ダイエットDAY
Ah, rolling and tumbling in bed, "I hate it, I hate it," on this pretty, pretty diet day!
曖昧一回楽に アイマイミー快楽に
Easy with ambiguity, easy with my "I-My-Me" pleasure,
病み悪化してんだって 愛だ 恋だ 何だてんだ
My sickness is worsening, they say it's love, romance, or whatever!
生命線は 愛だって 愛だ 嘆いたって
My lifeline is love, even if I lament that "it's love, it's love,"
ああでもない こうでもないな 寂しい寂しい ナンセンスDAY
"Not this, not that either," on this lonely, lonely nonsense day!
いっそ密会 ラフに 節操無い解：LOVE ME
Might as well have a casual secret meeting, with an unprincipled answer: "LOVE ME"
溺れ奴隷 踊れ 踊れ 亡霊だ
A drowning slave, dance, dance, I'm a ghost!
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない (ねえ)
There is nothing, nothing, I have nothing! (Hey!)
変われない 変われない 私変われない (ねえ)
I can't change, can't change, I can't change! (Hey!)
わからない わからない 「わかる」わからない (ねえ)
I don't understand, don't understand, "I understand," I don't understand! (Hey!)
はーい 目もと以外は 隠して
Yes, hide everything except for my eyes!
駄。ダダダダ ダリダリ ダーリン (funny)
No! Da-da-da-da, dar-dar-darling (funny)
はい 冴えない愛情論で おねだり
Yes, begging with a dull theory of love!
駄。ダダダダ ダーリン脳裏 dirty & dirty
No! Da-da-da-da, darling in my mind, dirty & dirty,
会いたい衝動 埋めてよ ダ ダ ダーリン
Fill this urge to meet you, da-da-darling!
無 無 nana 無 無 nana 無 na
Nai, nai, nana, nai, nai, nana, nai, na
無い無い清純 感情が 行ったり 来たり
There's no innocence, my emotions go back and forth!
無 無 nana 無 無 nana 無 na
Nai, nai, nana, nai, nai, nana, nai, na
無い無い純情 感情で 駄 ダ ダ ダーリン
No pure heart, with these emotions, no, da-da-darling!
ダダダダ ダーリンだ 愛だ 喘いだって
Da-da-da-da, it's darling, it's love, even if I gasp...
まあ 寝コロンゴロンて ニャニャ 食い意地 食い意地 ダイエットDAY
Well, rolling and tumbling in bed, "meow, meow," greed, greed, on this diet day!
もう 精神一杯で 詰み 暴論 お節介で 無理
My mind is at its limit, checkmate, crazy arguments and interference make it impossible!
病み垢してんだって 承認 承認 接待だ
Using my venting account, "approval, approval," it's just reception!
なともない なにもない 私なにもない (ねえ)
There is nothing, nothing, I have nothing! (Hey!)
はしたない はしたない 私はしたない (ねえ)
Improper, improper, I am so improper! (Hey!)
わからない わからない 「わかる」わからない (ねえ)
I don't understand, don't understand, "I understand," I don't understand! (Hey!)
はーい 自撮りは全部加工して
Yes, filter and edit all of my selfies!
駄。ダダダダ ダリダリ ダーリン (funny)
No! Da-da-da-da, dar-dar-darling (funny)
はい 絶えない愛情論で 冷めたり
Yes, cooling off with an endless theory of love!
駄。ダダダダ ダーリン無理 dirty & dirty
No! Da-da-da-da, darling, it's impossible, dirty & dirty,
会いたい衝動 止めてよ ダ ダ ダーリン
Stop this urge to meet you, da-da-darling!
踊れ (踊れ) 叫べ (叫べ)
Dance! (Dance!) Shout! (Shout!)
踊れ (踊れ) ルラッパパ (ルラッパパ)
Dance! (Dance!) Ru-ra-pa-pa! (Ru-ra-pa-pa!)
踊れ (踊れ) 唄え (唄え)
Dance! (Dance!) Sing! (Sing!)
踊れ (踊れ) ルラッパパ (ルラッパパ)
Dance! (Dance!) Ru-ra-pa-pa! (Ru-ra-pa-pa!)
もう ドッキン ドッキン 脳 しんど期 ドッキン 脳
Already thumping, thumping brain, a rough period, thumping brain,
はい 素顔は全部なくして
Yes, erase my real face completely!
駄。ダダダダ ダリダリ ダーリン (funny)
No! Da-da-da-da, dar-dar-darling (funny)
どうしようもない感情論に 喋ったり
Chatting over a hopeless theory of emotion!
駄。ダダダダ ダーリン脳裏 dirty & dummy
No! Da-da-da-da, darling in my mind, dirty & dummy,
会いたい衝動 埋めてよ ダ ダ ダーリン
Fill this urge to meet you, da-da-darling!
無 無 nana 無 無 nana 無 na
Nai, nai, nana, nai, nai, nana, nai, na
無い無い反応 返答を 期待したり
There's no response, hoping for a reply!
無 無 nana 無 無 nana 無 na
Nai, nai, nana, nai, nai, nana, nai, na
無い無い妄想 感情で 駄 ダ ダ ダーリン
With a non-existent delusional emotion, no, da-da-darling!
無い無い純情 感情で 駄 ダ ダ ダーリン
With a non-existent pure heart and emotion, no, da-da-darling!
ねえ ダーリンちゅ。
Hey, darling, chu!
待ち侘びている大通り
On the main street I've been waiting for,
目眩しそうな人混み
amidst the dizzying crowd,
くるり回った昼帯
the daytime spun around in a loop.
立ち止まってる坊坊
Standing still, boy,
しまい切れてない表情
with an expression you can't fully hide,
どこ見てるの坊坊
where are you looking, boy?
知らない
I don't know...
今なに
...what you're doing now.
目と目 止まった合図
Our eyes met, a signal to stop.
ロングのローリーズ
Long Lowrys,
「あとでね」
"Later," you said,
黒文字
in black letters.
隠してもムダね
It's no use hiding it.
けけけけーたいみしてよ 今から
S-s-s-show me your phone, starting now.
ねえ 今から
Hey, starting now.
ねえ いいでしょ
Hey, it's fine, right?
けーたいみしてよ
Show me your phone.
拒んでるの予想通り
You're refusing, just as expected,
だって賭けたこの試み
after all, I gambled on this attempt.
くるり回った昼帯
The daytime spun around in a loop.
立ち止まっていないで
Don't just stand there...
怒ったりしないでよ
...and don't get angry with me.
I need チュ
I need a kiss.
いらない
I don't need it,
I don't need it.
使い古しの愛も
Even your worn-out love,
言い訳たちも
and all your excuses.
画面じゃなくここ見て
Look here, not at your screen,
取り上げるからね
because I'm taking it away!
けけけけーたいみしてよ 今から
S-s-s-show me your phone, starting now.
ねえ 今から
Hey, starting now.
ねえ いいでしょう
Hey, it's fine, right?
けーたいかしてよ 今から
Lend me your phone, starting now.
けけけけーたいかしてよ 今から
S-s-s-lend me your phone, starting now.
ねえ 今すぐ
Hey, right now,
渡しなさい
hand it over.
ねえ いいでしょう
Hey, it's fine, right?
けーたいみしてよ！
Show me your phone!
Oh! You woke up!
Hi, good morning!
Did you have a good sleep?
Oh, here?
This is my room!
What was that?
It looks a bit different?
I guess you found out!
Ollie, um, prepared this room just for us!
Because it's a special room!
Yeah, um, I wanted to make our memory as special as possible, so...
I worked really hard, and I prepared the perfect scenery just for us!
Ollie even transported you here while you were still asleep.
I just didn't want you to be tired, is all.
I just love you so much that I want these feelings to properly reach you.
Huh? What's wrong?
...I'm not like my usual self?
You're so silly!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Oh! Wait!
Don't go! Where are you going?
Wow, I can't believe you ran away like that.
But you were so cute when you were so shy!
指切りげんまん ホラでも吹いたら
Pinky swear, if I tell even a single lie,
針でも何でも 飲ませていただき
I will swallow needles or whatever it takes.
Monday
It doesn't matter if it's Sunday
鏡よ鏡よ この世で1番
Mirror, mirror on the wall, who in this world...
変わることのない愛をくれるのはだれ
...would give me the most unchanging love of all?
No need to ask cause it's my darling
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than say goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのままおサラバするよか
Rather than say goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Still, sometimes my heart gets flighty
死んでも治らな治してみせます Baby
If it won't cure even in death, I'll show you I can cure it, baby
Yeah I ain't nothin but ya baby
失って初めて気がつくなんて
Realizing only after I've lost you
そんなダサいこともうしたないのよ goodbye
I don't want to do something so uncool anymore, goodbye
Oh don't you ever say byebye
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than say goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのままおサラバするよか
Rather than say goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
Ah
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than say goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのままおサラバするよか
Rather than say goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Still, sometimes my heart gets flighty
そんなダサいのはもう要らないのよ bye-bye
I don't need that corny shit anymore, bye-bye
I'll always stick wit ya my baby
I'll always stick with you, my baby
ねえアナタには見えない事ばかり
Hey, there are only things that you can't see
アタシは見えている事を知らないの？
Do you not know that I can see them?
背中につけられた誰かのキスの跡
The traces of someone's kiss left on your back
一人じゃ買う訳の無いそれも
And that thing you wouldn't buy alone
見て見ぬ振りなだけ
I'm just pretending not to see
だね
Right?
笑っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it makes you laugh
常時奔放 狂気 短気
Always wild, insane, short-tempered
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if you yell, one look and it's over
洗脳完了 女上手
Brainwash complete, she's a master
愛しているのさ
I love you
強く愛しているのさ
I love you so strongly
ねえ精神から全身まで
Hey, from my spirit to my whole body
表面から内面まで
From the outside to the inside
脳天から先端まで知りたいの
From head to toe, I want to know
それから最近聞いた音楽から
And also, from the music you recently listened to
散財した総額まで
To the total amount of money you spent
完全把握しないと気が済まないの
If I don't fully grasp it, I won't be satisfied
とやかく言ったって実際の問題は
No matter what you say, the actual problem is
その眼中アタシ何割くらい担ってるか
How much of an eye you keep on me
嗚呼隠してないで確信を頂戴
Ah, don't hide it, give me certainty
されど黙して語らず
But you remain silent and speechless
Bye-bye
困っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's troubling
容姿端麗 耽美 甘美
Beautiful appearance, aesthetic, sweet
身勝手だって泣くシックな素振り
Even if she's selfish, her crying is chic
瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Instantly drunk, the privilege of a woman
愛しちまうのさ
I end up loving you
されど愛しちまうのさ
But I end up loving you anyway
過去を喰らう程にポップなエレジー
A pop elegy that eats up the past
排気口から香るコールドラーメン
Cold ramen smelling from the exhaust vent
騙し奪われる恋でもいいの
It's fine even if it's a love where I'm deceived and robbed
だってこの声は
Because this voice is...
めっちゃくちゃ可愛いでしょ？
...super-duper cute, right?
笑っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it makes you laugh
常時奔放 狂気 短気
Always wild, insane, short-tempered
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if you yell, one look and it's over
洗脳完了 女上手
Brainwash complete, she's a master
困っちまう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's troubling
容姿端麗 耽美 甘美
Beautiful appearance, aesthetic, sweet
身勝手だって泣くシックな素振り
Even if she's selfish, her crying is chic
瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Instantly drunk, the privilege of a woman
愛しているのさ
I love you
強く愛しているのさ
I love you so strongly
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl...
誘惑される
...tempted by...
鼓動に
...the heartbeat.
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
A toast of love to...
愛を乾杯
...the bursting conflict,
伝えられなくても
even if it can't be conveyed.
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl...
誰かを穿って
...piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を
harboring your clear eyes...
孕んで
...Harbors them.
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Come, carve out some flashy steps.
仕事帰りの疲れは
Leave the fatigue from work...
私と、このグラスに
...with me and this glass.
さあ 自分好みに縫って
Come, sew it to your liking.
世間に対する気持ち
Your feelings toward the world...
私に注いでみない？
...won't you pour them into me?
ありがちなラブソングでも
Even in a cliché love song,
愛が込められてるの
love is poured into it.
それでも汚れるのね
Even so, it gets stained, doesn't it?
君を見れば分かるの
I can tell just by looking at you.
下を向く君の目を
I won't try to force open...
無理矢理剥ごうとはしない
...your eyes looking downward.
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸べて ほら
So don't make that face; reach out your hand, look.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl,
誘惑される鼓動に
tempted by the heartbeat.
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast of love to the bursting conflict,
伝えられなくても
even if it can't be conveyed.
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl,
誰かを穿って
piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を
harboring your clear eyes...
孕んで
...Harbors them.
君の愛を知った気で ハイになっていて
Feeling like I've known your love, getting high,
感度去っていて 毎回泣いていてさ
sensibility fades, crying every single time.
それくらいがいいんでしょ
That's just about right, isn't it?
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Come, carve out some flashy steps.
君の顔色今では
Since your complexion now...
マシになってきてるから
...has gotten a whole lot better.
君に委ねるわ Bunny Girl
I'll leave it to you, Bunny Girl.
私をあげるわ Bunny Girl
I'll give you myself, Bunny Girl,
誘惑される
tempted by...
鼓動に
...the heartbeat.
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
A toast of love to...
愛を乾杯
...the bursting conflict,
伝えられてるはず
it must have been conveyed.
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl,
誰かを穿って
piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を
harboring your clear eyes...
孕んで
...Harbors them.
わっ！
Surprise!
見つけた！ずっと探してたんだ！
There you are! I was looking everywhere for you!
かくれんぼしてるなんて教えてくれなかったじゃないか～
You didn't tell me we were playing hide-and-seek!
やった～！ついにオリーのネオンステージに来てくれたんだね！
Well, I see you've made it to my neon stage!
どうかな？キラキラしてて可愛いでしょ？
How do you like it? It's really pretty, right?
全力で頑張って作ったんだよ～！ネオンもいっぱいあるの！
I put a lot of effort into it! It's got lots of neons and whatnot!
君が隠れてる間にね、こっそりお着替えもしちゃったの！
And while you were hiding, I had the time to change my clothes!
オリー、めっちゃ可愛くなったでしょ～？
Don't I look super cute?
へへ～ まだまだ君のために準備したものがたくさんあるんだ～
Hehe, yeah! And I still have a lot that I prepared for you!
だから、このかくれんぼはもう終わりにしよ～？
So, I hope that we can put an end to this hide-and-seek!
えっ？ダメなの？
Huh? No?
ねえ...
Hey...
ここに来てから、なんだまずっと様子がおかしいよ？
Since we got here, you've been acting really weird...
ここに来てから、なんだかずっと様子がおかしいよ？
You've been acting really weird ever since you got here, and...
オリー、全然わからないよ...
I... I just don't understand!
いつも投稿にいいねしたりコメントしたりして、オリーの気を引こうとしてたんでしょ？
You've been trying to get my attention by liking my posts and commenting on them...
これが欲しかったんじゃないの？
Isn't this what you wanted?
オリーのこと、好きなんでしょ？
You... You love me, right?
もっと一緒にいたいって思わないの？
Don't you want to spend more time with me?
どうしてオリーの気持ちを受け入れてくれないの...？喜ぶはずなのに...
Why are you not accepting my feelings? You're supposed to be happy! But...
なんでそんな変な行動をとるの...？
...you're acting so strange!
ちょっ！待って！
Ah! Wa- Wait, wait, wait!
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your end-of-service is hitting me hard...
どんだけ泣いたかわかんないや
I don't even know how much I've cried.
つら 雑魚りっぱ
It's tough. A splendid loser.
ぽっかり空いて埋まらないや
There's a gaping hole that won't be filled.
ほしい ラブぴったん
I want the perfect love.
中中中中っ途な出会いじゃ刺さんないや
A half-hearted encounter just won't cut it.
やっぱり無理かも ばたんきゅー
As expected, I can't do this... I'm out cold.
げっそりハートが治んないや
My worn-out heart won't heal.
出してよすぐ処方箋
Give me a prescription right now.
サヨナラの棘 なんで抜けないの
Why can't I pull out the thorn of goodbye?
きみの代わりの人形が 全然見つからない
I can't find a substitute doll for you at all.
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん！
Sad Girl Sex!
ウブの出棺 好きってどんな想いだっけなぁ
The coffin of naivety. What did it feel like to love?
誰かと寝ても寂しさが発火
Even if I sleep with someone, loneliness ignites.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your end-of-service is hitting me hard...
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん！
Sad Girl Sex!
ラブの接待 「きっとまた会える」なんてさぁ
The hospitality of love. Saying "We'll surely meet again"...
思い出のきみに食い殺されっ子
I'm just a kid being eaten alive by memories of you.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your end-of-service is hitting me hard...
ねえマンガ返してよ 最新話であのキャラ死んじゃったよ
Hey, return my manga. That character died in the latest chapter!
教えてくれたバンド メンバーがクスリで捕まっちゃったよ
The band you recommended... a member got busted for drugs!
一緒にいたこと消えないや
The times we spent together won't fade away.
全部が二人だった
Everything was about the two of us.
きっときみは今誰かといるの
Surely you're with someone else right now.
あたしだけが課金中
And I'm the only one still paying for it.
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん！
Sad Girl Sex!
ウブの出棺 嫉妬辛くてエンバってらぁ
The coffin of naivety. Jealousy hurts, so I'm embalming it.
上書きがしたい どうしてくれるの
I want to overwrite it. What are you going to do about it?
愛のガチャガチャ 天井はない
The gacha of love has no pity limit.
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん！
Sad Girl Sex!
ラブの没収 ちょっとエグすぎない？ほんとさぁ
The confiscation of love. Isn't that a bit too cruel? Seriously.
涙の跡に狂気が走った
Madness ran through the traces of my tears.
愛のガチャガチャ 天井はない
The gacha of love has no pity limit.
もしもが叶う素敵世界ならば
If this were a wonderful world where "what ifs" came true,
きみはサヨナラ取り下げを 検討加速しちゃう？
would you accelerate your plans to withdraw your goodbye?
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん！
Sad Girl Sex!
ウブの出棺 なんでこんな終わってんだろ
The coffin of naivety. Why did it end like this?
誰かと寝たら埋められるような
Is this the level of love that can be filled
レベルの愛だ？そんなんじゃない！
just by sleeping with someone? It's not like that!
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん！
Sad Girl Sex!
ラブでぺっちゃんこ 今でも想ってんだわ
Crushed flat by love, yet I still think of you.
期待寄りの地獄 もう戻れないの
A hell built on expectations. I can't go back anymore.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your end-of-service is hitting me hard...
サガセ 続行 だめだめ波ぁ
Search and continue! No-no wave!
揺らせ 絶頂 あせあせ弾
Shake it up to climax! Sweaty bullet!
サガセ 続行 だめだめ波ぁ
Search and continue! No-no wave!
きみの絶交 効いてんだみょん
Your rejection is hitting me hard...
檻の中 あたしの
Inside the cage, my...
愛猫
beloved kitty cat.
お帰りなさい 君にニャオ
Welcome back home, crying "meow" to you.
悪い子ね 汚れたお身体で
You're a naughty child, with that tainted body.
行きはよいよいで帰りは怖い
Going is easy, but returning is scary.
愛を知らない飽き猫さん
The bored cat who knows nothing of love.
間抜けにゃーい
Silly meow!
愛嬌とか そりゃ結構
Flattery and charms? No thanks.
睨めっこ ほらバレバレで
Staring contest... look, it's totally obvious.
もう 躁 なんで？お仕置きだ 自己嫌悪
Another manic episode? Why? It's punishment, self-loathing.
君は あたしだけの愛猫
You are my beloved kitty, mine alone.
ダンダン好キニナル 好キニナル
Slowly, slowly falling for you, falling for you...
気になる気になる
I'm curious, I'm curious...
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me...
だんだん好きになる
Gradually falling for you...
気になる
I'm curious...
好きになる 好きになるね
I'll fall for you, I'm falling for you...
愛して
Love me.
可愛いね 首輪つけてにゃお
You're so cute, put on this collar, meow.
大切に愛でてあげるにゃお
I'll cherish and pamper you, meow.
檻の中の子猫ちゃん
The little kitten inside the cage...
愛のランデブー さあ踊りましょう
Our love rendezvous, come, let's dance!
喉鳴らし擦り寄って ほらどうぞ？
Purring, snuggling up... Go on, show me?
睨めっこ あら甘えん坊さん
A staring contest? My, what a spoiled baby.
そっぽ向いてもそりゃ結構
Even if you look away, that's perfectly fine.
君はあたしだけの愛猫さん
You're my one and only beloved cat.
だんだん好きになる
Gradually falling for you...
気になる気になる
I'm curious, I'm curious...
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me...
だんだん好きになる
Gradually falling for you...
気になる
I'm curious...
好きになる 好きになるね
I'll fall for you, I'm falling for you...
愛して
Love me.
逃げられやしないの 馬鹿ね
You can't run away, you silly thing.
一生の愛が死ぬの 愛して
A lifetime of love is dying, love me.
最後にはだって君は愛猫さん
In the end, you're still my beloved cat.
Halooo? Where are you?
Ugh, come out!
I thought we were done playing hide and seek.
Gosh, where could you be?
Show yourself!
Hah, I can't believe that you would make me look for you like this.
Hmm...
Ah!
I found you!
Don't go anywhere now!
ほとばしる香る君のその髪が
The fragrance of your hair...
僕の心を踊らせたんです
made my heart dance.
翳くだけ 今はそれだけで
Just fluttering, for now, just with that...
この身 屈めますから
I will bow this body.
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight ray Darling...
堪えきれぬ欲望に任せて
leaving it to irresistible desires.
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight ray Darling...
僕に仕える気になったら
If you feel like serving me...
はあ
Ah...
願うは三度の絶頂を
I wish for three peaks...
胸の中で至る
reaching within my chest.
今宵も僕らは繁栄の<
Tonight too, we...
ために愛を放つ
release love for the sake of prosperity.
抗いの呟きとは裏腹に
Contrary to the murmur of resistance...
身体は嬉しそうに動いたんです
my body moved happily.
この翼に輪を付けるかは
Whether to put a ring on these wings...
僕ら次第ですから
depends on us.
真面目ですかな
Are you serious?
淫らですかな
Or are you lewd?
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight ray Darling...
愛と欲に純白を求めて
seeking pure white in love and desire.
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight ray Darling...
僕を拒む気になっても
even if you feel like rejecting me.
はあ
Ah...
願うは三度の絶頂を
I wish for three peaks...
胸の中で至る
reaching within my chest.
零れる涙が飽和して
Spilling tears reach saturation...
僕は今に果てる
I am perishing now.
その溢れた吐息の原因なんだって？
What is the cause of that overflowing sigh?
いったいどこからいったって？ ドキドキなんだって？
Where on earth is it from? Is it because you're excited?
よろめく恐怖が原因なんだって？
Is the trembling fear the cause?
それでも君ならいいんだって
Even so, if it's you, it's fine.
さらに
And even more...
はあ
Ah...
願うは三度の絶頂を
I wish for three peaks...
胸の中で至る
reaching within my chest.
今宵も僕らは繁栄の
Tonight too, we...
愛をもっとスライスしてよ　ハッ
Slice my love even more, ha!
願うは三度の絶頂を
I wish for a three-fold climax
胸の中で至る
reaching inside my chest.
零れる涙が飽和して
Overflowing tears saturate
ぼくは今に果てる
and I'm about to perish right now.
ねぇあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know...
君がひとり知ってるの知ってるよ
...that you're all alone. I know it, I know.
ビクンビクン震えてさ 声もダダ漏れなんだわ
Twitching and trembling, your voice is totally leaking out.
正直にいっちゃえよ バレてるんだしいっちゃえよ
Just tell the truth, it's already exposed, just say it.
効いてんの？
Is it working?
普通普通恥ずかしい？ みんな隠しているだけ
Is it normally, normally embarrassing? Everyone's just hiding it.
ムフッ
*giggles*
ねぇあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know...
君がひとり涙してるの知ってるよ
...that you're all alone crying. I know.
グスングスン凹んでさ 弱い人から in the night
Sniffling and depressed, showing weakness in the night.
朝が来るまで一緒コース
Together on a course until morning comes.
もっと泣いたって
Even if you cry more,
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll accept you as many times as it takes.
もう我慢しないで いっぱい出しねね
Don't hold back anymore, let it all out.
Mwah!
お願い君が欲しいの
Please, I want you so bad.
慰めさせて　シェイク シェイク　愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, shake shake, with my talent of love.
泣いてくれなきゃ
If you don't cry for me,
枯れてしまう
I'll wither away,
濡れていたい
I want to stay wet.
ねぇいいでしょう？
Hey, is that okay?
舐めとって飲み干したいんだってば
I want to lick it up and drink it all down, I tell you!
Mwah!
お願い君が欲しいの
Please, I want you so bad.
頼り散らして シックラブ なんて最高ね
Rely on me, sick love is just the best.
分けてくれないか_
Won't you share it with me?
君の「痛い」
Your \"pain\"?
感じていたい
I want to feel it.
ねぇいいでしょう？
Hey, is that okay?
吸い取って救いたいんだってば
I want to suck it out and save you, I tell you!
見たい 見たい 見たい...
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see...
君の中
...inside of you.
見たい 見たい 見たい...
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see...
ねぇあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know...
君がひとり悔しがってんの知ってるよ
...that you're all alone feeling frustrated. I know.
ズキュンズキュン高まるじゃん 君を推すことをやめない
My heart throbs, I won't stop supporting you.
ねぇあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know...
君はできる子知ってるよ
...you can do it, I know.
つらいときは弱いくらいで丁度いい
When it's tough, showing weakness is just right.
あたしそれでも好きだよ
I still love you regardless.
Mwah!
お願い君が欲しいの
Please, I want you so bad.
名前を呼んでよ
Call my name,
いつだって会いに参上
and I'll come to see you anytime.
君はひとりだ だから歌う「ひとりじゃない」
You're alone, so I'll sing \"You're not alone.\"
もういいでしょう
Isn't that enough already?
ソロプレイはおしまいなんだってば
Solo play is over, I tell you!
君がやめるときも　あたし側にいるわ
Even when you give up, I'll be by your side.
いつも見守っているわ
I'll always be watching over you.
そうよ怖くないのよ
Yes, there's nothing to fear.
あぁーーー
Ahhh...
Mwah!
お願い君が欲しいの
Please, I want you so bad.
慰めさせて　シェイク シェイク　愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, shake shake, with my talent of love.
泣いてくれなきゃ
If you don't cry for me,
枯れてしまう
I'll wither away,
濡れていたい
I want to stay wet.
ねぇいいでしょう？
Hey, is that okay?
舐めとって飲み干したいんだってば
I want to lick it up and drink it all down, I tell you!
Mwah!
お願い君が欲しいの
Please, I want you so bad.
頼り散らして シックラブ なんて最高ね
Rely on me, sick love is just the best.
分けてくれないか
Won't you share it with me?
君の「痛い」
Your \"pain\"?
感じていたい
I want to feel it.
ねぇいいでしょう？
Hey, is that okay?
吸い取って救いたいんだってば
I want to suck it out and save you, I tell you!
ねぇあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know...
君がひとり涙してるの知ってるよ
...that you're all alone crying. I know.
グスングスン凹んでさ 弱い人から in the night
Sniffling and depressed, showing weakness in the night.
朝が来るまで一緒コース
Together on a course until morning comes.
もっと泣いたって
Even if you cry more,
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll accept you as many times as it takes.
もう我慢しないで 出して
Don't hold back anymore, let it out...
さあ
...come on.
Phew! Fuw!
Finally done!
Wow!
This way you won't be running away anymore~
Now be good and sit tight, okay?
Haaah... You really made me work up a sweat.
You made me look for you, chase you down...
But I'm just glad that we're finally together again.
Now we get to spend some time together!
Just the two of us! Hehehe.
Hey! Pay attention! Look at me.
Hmm... That's a good boy. I mean, that's a good boy! Hehe.
Alright, now that I have your attention,
I can finally show you what I've been working on all this time!
Check this out! Yay!
今回も誕生日グッズが出ます！
We're releasing birthday merchandise this year too!
Kami juga bakal ada merchandise yang baru!
We also have new merchandise!
Ollie akan perkenalkan satu-satu ya!
Ollie will introduce them one by one!
Yeah, there will also be birthday goods
for this year, so I'll be introducing
it to you guys one by one, okay? Hai!
it to you guys one by one, okay? Yes!
Yeah, the first item will be... Kochira!
Yeah, the first item will be... this!
Wow! It's a wide rubber mat!
Isn't this so cute? So that whenever...
...working, wherever you're gaming,
you always remember me.
The theme, it kind of looks like a yandere, doesn't it?
But I'm not a yandere, I'm just your girlfriend.
Yeah, it's wide,
slightly large-sized rubber mat recommended for everyday use!
And the illustration is by 花澤あきら先生！
And the illustration is by Hanazawa Akira-sensei!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
Okay, then the next item will be... こちら！
Okay, then the next item will be... this!
Wow, it's a pillow! Isn't this so cute?
クッションだよ、bandages!
It's a cushion, with bandages!
So that when you're sleeping,
you remember me, you dream of me.
This, it looks so fluffy, so you guys better get it for a good night's sleep.
All right, and followed by... こちら！
All right, and followed by... this!
It's a ring necklace!
Well, it's a ring, if it doesn't fit your size, you can just wear it as a necklace, isn't that really cool?
そう、これはね、指輪。
Yes, this is a ring.
でも、サイズが合ってないなら、ネックレスでも使えるの
But if it doesn't fit your size, you can still use it as a necklace...
ことが出来ます！
...which is awesome!
It's so cute! So make sure that when you go out, you wear this!
So that whenever you go grocery shopping, no other girls out there will be hitting on you.
はい！ And then, we also have... こちら！
Yes! And then, we also have... this!
It's a mug! Isn't this so cute? I really like the design!
So, not only when you're working,
or gaming, or grocery shopping, or sleeping,
but even when you're drinking, you think of me.
And of course, not forgetting...
こちら！
this!
Situational voice pack in three languages!
in 日本語, in Bahasa Indonesia, and English!
in Japanese, in Indonesian, and English!
Wow, as always... さすがに、さすが me!
Wow, as always... just as expected of me!
はい！そして最後に、フルセットを購入いただいた方には、
Yes! And finally, for those who purchase the full set,
数量限定で、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
a limited quantity of handwritten autographed instant photo-style cards will be included!
And for those of you guys who buy the full set, there will be
limited edition postcard with my message and my sign!
a limited edition postcard with my message and my sign!
Ya! Jadi bagi yang beli full set-nya ini, bakal dapet
Yes! So for those who buy the full set, you will get
postcard dari Ollie, ada message, ada tanda tangannya juga!
a postcard from Ollie with a message and signature!
Yes!
次は、通常版は
Next, the normal version comes with
箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
a foil-stamped replica autographed instant photo-style card!
For those of you who buy like the normal version, you guys can also get the postcard
with my sign and message!
Yang beli versi biasa juga akan dapet postcard yang ada message dan sign-nya!
Those who buy the normal version will also get a postcard with a message and signature!
Okay, that is all!
That was a mouthful, wasn't it?
But you'll buy my merch, won't you?
That's what I like to hear!
Wish I could spend more time with you, but
unfortunately, our time is limited. Mmm.
But, I have one last thing that I'd like to gift to you.
So I hope you'll pay attention and wait for me, okay? Don't go anywhere!
Hehehe.
私をみて
Look at me.
声を聞いて
Listen to my voice.
私をみて
Look at me.
私だけをみて
Look only at me.
ユルサナイ
I won't forgive you.
ゾッとした表情が可愛いね
Your terrified expression is cute.
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours.
Love it? ナニに ラリって
Love it? What are you high on?
愛 High 哀想ね
Love, high, how pathetic.
君は悪い子なのだ
You're a bad boy.
どの娘がお好きで？ 散々に
Which girl do you like? Terribly so,
色目がお上手で 頭湧き
you're so good at flirting, you're out of your mind.
君に踊らされちゃって アタシは狂う
Manipulated by you, I'm going crazy.
What is love it?
君の血肉まで
To your flesh and blood,
骨の髄まで
to the marrow of your bones.
挿れて 空っぽになる 愛のパペッ卜
Plunging in and becoming empty, a puppet of love.
胸が苦しいね
Your chest feels tight, doesn't it?
息が詰まるのね
You're suffocating, aren't you?
それが恋と 教えてあげる あはは
Let me teach you that's love, ahaha.
虚ろな声で
With a hollow voice,
ほら 囁いて
come on, whisper to me.
いい子ね 首輪付けた 君は Love it
Good boy, with a collar on, you're "Love it."
イカれちゃったのね
Have you gone mad?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, you see.
したいよね してあげるわ イッて あはは
You want to do it, don't you? I'll do it for you, go on, ahaha.
濡れて 君の赤い生液 溺れるまで
Getting wet, until you drown in your red fluids.
イタイ イタイのトンデユケ 死んで詫びるまで
Pain, pain, fly away! Until you apologize by dying.
愚かね 愚かね 間抜けな面して
How foolish, how foolish, with that dumb look on your face...
君は悪い子なの
You are a bad kid.
痛いのがお好きで？ サにサに
You like it when it hurts? So sadistic, so sadistic.
あら お口はチャックで 何 何？
Oh, zip your mouth shut. What is it, what is it?
性に踊らされちゃう
Danced around by lust,
君を喰らう
I'll devour you.
君の血肉まで
To your flesh and blood,
骨の髄まで
to the marrow of your bones,
しゃぶりつくせばもう空っぽの
if I suck you dry, you'll be empty...
パペット
a puppet.
胸が苦しいね
My chest feels tight, doesn't it?
息が詰まるのね
You're suffocating, aren't you?
それが恋と教えてあげる
I'll teach you that that is love!
君はピエロね
You're a clown, aren't you?
愛を囁いて
Whispering love,
人間の形した君はラヴ
you, in human form, are love.
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone mad, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, isn't it?
したいよね してあげるわ 誓って？
You want to do it, don't you? I'll do it for you. Swear it?
報い 救えない 穢れた血に溺れるまで
Retribution, beyond saving, until drowning in defiled blood,
痛い 痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
pain, pain, go away, until my breath stops.
報い 救えない 穢れた血に溺れるまで
Retribution, beyond saving, until drowning in defiled blood,
痛い 痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
pain, pain, go away, until my breath stops.
CAST: hololive Indonesia
Kureiji Ollie (holoro) / Vestia Zeta (holoh3ro)
CAST: hololive 4th generation
Amane Kanata
CAST: hololive English
Takanashi Kiara (Myth)
CAST: HOLOSTARS
Minase Rio (UPROAR!!)
Special guest
Michi Mochievee
CREDIT: Thumbnail - k3nzoteruya
3D Animation - OCTOLOID
Tuning, Mix, Mastering - Kururu
Lyric Overlay - Maad
SNS Promotion Assets - Altersky
Choreography - FreeM
Special thanks
トライフロンティア合同会社 / すくろーす / クックルP / aS / 合同会社VESSEL LIFE / um.
[Trifrontier LLC / Sucrose / Kukku-ru P / aS / VESSEL LIFE LLC / um.]
暁 / Koudai / Toshiyuki / sa-sara / etc.
[Akatsuki / Koudai / Toshiyuki / sa-sara / etc.]
Thank you so much for coming
to watch the 3D Birthday Live!
How was it? Did you feel my love?
Oh, look at that!
It's the specially prepared bedroom! Cute, isn't it?
It has a bed, a sofa, Udin, and...
I don't know if you noticed, but there was a
display photo of the people I cherished most in there.
Did you catch it?
I think the neon stage was really cool too!
You probably spotted a bunch of TVs sitting around.
And, well, those are there to help me watch you from afar.
Cool, right?
Ah, but come to think of it,
I really did drag you around the stages, huh?
Um, how are you? Do you feel sick?
Are you okay?
I'm a bit worried, but I think
it shouldn't affect you too much,
since I carried you while you were still sleeping.
Huh? What? No, nothing! I didn't say anything!
Um, speaking of you, you kept running
and hiding away from me.
Naughty, naughty!
You always leave comments and like every post I make,
so I thought you'd like it if I came to visit.
I didn't think it would actually surprise you that much!
I think maybe it was because you were too surprised
when I suddenly appeared in front of you.
Yeah, hmm...
But just so you know, I worked really hard just for you!
I practiced my singing, I sang a lot,
and changed my outfits so many times!
And, I wonder if my feelings reached you.
It obviously did, right?
Also, at the end, I finally managed to catch you!
That's what you hoped for, right?
I mean, cause you were running away from me
because you love me a lot.
Obviously you were expecting it too, right?
Hehe, period!
Anyway, for those of you who are still watching,
thank you by the way. I have an announcement!
I'll be featured in SO87's song, "Love Me Back",
with a music video!
It's going to be so cool! So keep an eye out, okay?
Ah, it's just so exciting, isn't it?
If you ever feel the need to feel my love again,
then don't hesitate and please come back
to watch the 3D Birthday Live again, okay?
I'll always be here waiting for you!
Anyways, bye-bye!
Otsucrazy!
わっはー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Wa-ha, We're zombie zombies
「死にたい死にたい」って死んでるじゃん
You say, "I want to die, I want to die," but you're already dead
なのに「会いたい会いたい」が消えないじゃん
Yet "I want to see you, I want to see you" won't disappear
いつだって痛いの痛いの飛んでいかないの なんでなんで
The pain, the pain, it never flies away, why, oh why?
寂しさだけ残っちゃってるんだ
Only the loneliness remains
わっはー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Wa-ha, We're zombie zombies
傷を縫って 蜜を塗って
Stitch the wounds, paint the honey
何度だって 恋をするコーデ
Styling myself to fall in love again and again
傷擦って 蜜を吸って
Rubbing the wounds, sucking the nectar
何度だって 恋がしたい
Over and over again, I want to be in love
あたしなっちゃってるの
I've gone and become one
あいらびゅー 腐りかけもいいね
I love you, even starting to rot is nice
きみもなっちゃえば？
Why don't you become one too?
あいらびゅー ふたりだけのシークレット
I love you, our little secret
わっはー We're ゾンビゾンビ
Wa-ha, We're zombie zombies
ドッキドキがもう聞こえない
My heartbeat can't be heard anymore
わっはー We're ゾンビゾンビ
Wa-ha, We're zombie zombies
ぎゅっしても冷たいまま
Even if we hug tightly, it remains cold